(Sheldon:)A juvenile amalgamation
of our names.
Sheldon, Amy-- Shamy.
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Amy:)I don't like that.
(Amy:)Don't do that.
(awkward chuckle)
(Penny:)All righty. What's new?
(Amy:)Well, just recently, I learned
that you refer to us as Shamy,
(Amy:)and I don't like that.
(Penny:)I got it.
(Penny:)But what I was going for was,
you know, how's your life?
(Amy:)Like everybody else's.
(Amy:)Subject to entropy,
decay and eventual death.
(Amy:)Thank you for asking.
(Amy:)Why is she not taking our order?
(Sheldon:)I should've warned you,
(Sheldon:)one has to navigate a
labyrinth of social nonsense
(Sheldon:)before one can be fed here.
AMY: Really?
(Amy:)I assumed an establishment called
(Amy:)the Cheesecake Factory would
function more efficiently.
(Sheldon:)It's how they lure you in.
I believe it's called "
bait and switch."
(Penny:)Okay, I'm just gonna walk away,
(Penny:)'cause... I don't want to be here.
(Leonard:)So, this is nice.
(Leonard:)First time we've all
gotten together to eat.
(Amy:)You're right, he's a
festival of humdrum chitchat.